Subtitle Created By : Mostofa Kamal
Mostofa_Kamal_86@yahoo.com
www.Facebook.com/Mostofa.kamal.86
I'll check him tomorrow
Mister Sinha, this is a case
of liver cirrhosis
The liver is badly damaged.
The patient is under observation
It's difficult to say anything yet
But, you can do something?
The problem is, we can't do a liver
transplant... on such short notice
If you wish to inform her
family or relatives...
...you may use my phone
Hey buddy, how are you?
Where are you?
I'm at the hospital
Hospital! Are you okay?
Ya, I'm OK
So, what's wrong then?
Just hang in there. I'm coming
By the way, Akash is back in Bombay.
I'll bring him along
He won't come
Don't be silly. Forget what happened
He'll be very happy to
know you're here.
Ya Sameer, tell me
Maybe you should go meet him alone.
I don't want to come.
You are right.
Let bygones be bygones...
But what's happening now
isn't wrong either, is it?
I am living my life and Sid his
I really think you should
go meet him alone
Sameer, come home quickly.
Now. At once
Sameer! Akash! What's wrong?
What's the rush?
How do you like it?
Have you gone mad?
On the phone you sounded like somebody's
broken into your house!
What do you mean beautiful!?
But Sid... don't you think
she resembles someone?
Resembles whom?
What do you think, Sameer?
I think everybody resembles
some one or the other.
But she resembles Miss. Kashyap
Our Economics teacher?
Yes, sir. Our Economics teacher
No man!
Ya man. I know Miss. Kashyap
better than you
Tuitions...
I used to go to her for tuitions
At these tuitions, were there other
students or just the two of you?
What do you think?
- Just the two of you?
You are right, Akash
She does resemble Miss. Kashyap.
But guess where I've messed up?
You've got her figure wrong
What do you know about her figure?
I'm looking for Sid
Sinha... Siddharth Sinha
When did you return to Bombay?
- This morning.
Can't imagine what 'd have
happened if I wasn't here
How is she now?
Don't know. It's hard to say
Tell me about you.
What're you up to these days?
I'm working with Dad in his
computer business
Everything else is the same...
And you? Still at your uncle's place
in Poona?
Ya. It's a very nice.
You must come there sometime
Definitely man
Are you just saying that or
do you really intend on coming?
I intend on doing a lot of things
...like getting married
I always knew that the first to ge
married among us three would be you
Guess what! So is Akash
What! Akash! Getting married!?
That's funny
I'm not kidding!
No way!
But to whom? That girl who was
crazy about him in college?
Don't you remember her?
She used to say Akash's name
in that peculiar way!
God! Deepa is coming here!
Akash, let's dance. It'll make the
other couples jealous
Sure! Why not! Go ahead.
I'll be right with you
In three lifetimes from now
Sameer, please get me a drink.
I'm ever so thirsty
And throw in a dance or two with
Deepa while you're at it
What're you sketching?
Priya, isn't Sameer taking too
long to get your drink?
Did somebody just die?
- Yes... you!
Did I send you to get a drink
or chat up other girls!
I'm sure you have something
going on with her
I remember you were never home
when I was away on holiday
You've got it all wrong, Priya
How do you know her?
Did somebody just die?
Who is she?
- I don't know
You must have seen her somewhere!
That I have.
- Where?
She's over there
Priya, do you know her?
Forget it man. She doesn't
seem your type
I don't plan on marrying her!
Big deal about my type
And may I know what your type is?
One who lives her life
and lets me live mine
Someone not overtly emotional
Oh, I remember.
You once met such a girl
The affair lasted for two weeks!
That itself was too much
Anyway, I'm off...
...or she'll have had grandchildren
by the time I get there
Think about it.
I don't see her biting the hook
It's called the good-ole
Akash charm and it never fails
Is the mike leaking., where has 3 gone?
Today, on this all important
graduation day...
I have decided to sing a song
And because we are stepping
into a new world...
...where the responsibility to be
somebody will be thrust on us...
The title of the song is:
"A hundred ways to get a job"
Relax guys! I was only kidding!
If people say... that we are crazy,
then let them
We don't give a damn
about what they think
When we can play music
When we can sing...
Then why should we hesitate?
We will sing the melody
that's in our hearts
If the world gets angry...
- Let it be angry
If the world quarrels...
- Let it quarrel
If the world fights...
- Just it fight.
Just keep right on singing
If the world sulks...
- Let it sulk
If ties are broken...
- Let them break
If someone leaves you...
- Let them go
Don't ever be afraid
We are today.
Why should our style be old?
There's lightning in our eyes.
A storm in our breath
What's fear, what's defeat?
We don't know what they mean
The earth and sky,
are created for us
I'm sure we could even
pluck the stars out of the night
Our abode is beyond the sky
We are today.
Why should our style be old?
We have been raised in the
land of dreams
We can be as shy as
we are openly affectionate
Mesmerising everybody
wherever we go...
...teaching you lovely women
the art of love
We know how to steal
a woman's heart and her sleep
We are today.
Why should our style be old?
If people say...
...that we are crazy, then let them
We don't give a damn
about what they think
When we can play music
When we can sing...
Then why should we hesitate?
We will sing the melody
that's in our hearts
If the world gets angry...
- Let it be angry
If the world quarrels...
- Let it quarrel
If the world fights...
- Let it fight
Just keep right on singing
If the world sulks...
- Let it sulk
If ties are broken...
- Let them break
If someone leaves you...
- Let them go
Don't ever be afraid
We are today.
Why should our style be old?
Shalini... that's a lovely name
I haven't seen you before.
You're not from our college
You're right. I'm here with somebody
And now would you say yes to
dancing with this somebody?
The fact is that Rohit...
Rohit! Okay!
So you are Rohit's sister?
No. Actually I...
Rohit and I are very good friends.
Why, he's more like a brother
Not even if I told you
that I love you?
Yes, Shalini. I love you
and only you
My every breath...
...every heartbeat...
...every moment,
is for you, Shalini
I'm sure that I was born
so that I could love you
And you were born to become mine
You are mine, Shalini
And if you ask your heart...
...you will know that I speak
the truth.
Who are you?
Don't you recognize your brother Rohit?
You are Rohit? I mean,
you too- are Rohit?
I thought Shalini was that
other Rohit's sister.
Look, he's over there
Sameer...! Your name is Sameer?
So you've being lying to me all along!
That's really wrong of you
What can I say now...
You can see for yourself
He got me to believe that
his name was Rohit
Neither is he Rohit
nor Shalini my sister
Shalini is my fiancee
Fiancee...!
I don't like you being friends
with Akash at all
His behaviour the other night...
You know how embarrassed I was?
Let him do what he wants.
Just keep away from him
But Akash is my friend, Priya!
Like you don't have
any other friends?
Yes, I do... But he...
Just decide, Sameer. You can
either be with Akash or me!
I am thinking...
You need time to think
if you want to be with me!
Okay. So you want some time?
No!
I'm going out with friends.
I'll be back by 2.00
If I don't hear from you before that,
I'll know what your answer is
Don't you think you are
over-reacting?
No
You've never seen me over-react.
If I do... then God help you!!
What are you doing!
Your bruise has turned a strange colour.
Have you seen it, Sid?
I'm glad you like it!
Do you want one?
Hey! Don't get that anger out on me man
Did I ask you to speak to Shalini?
No. But you could've at least helped me.
You just sat there!
Such a true friend! I think I'd be
better off befriending Rohit
I'd at least get some protection!
May God bless your unity. I'm off.
Where to? -Home.
Why? What's the hurry?
Right, Sameer?
Ya, man, chill. It's only
1'O' clock
In which country?
It's nearly 4 here!
I forgot to call Priya!
Why are you so scared of Priya?
I'm not scared of her
I don't want to hurt her
or lose her
Sameer, I can't understand
how you tolerate her
She seems more a boss
than a girlfriend!
Akash, I'm asking for help,
not your expert comments
What should I do?
What do you think?
I'll tell you what.
Call Priya and apologise
Tell her you will never meet
Akash again
You know I won't do that!
What if she gets hurt...
What if you lose her!
You'll never improve, will you
Why are you turning this
into such an issue?
Just call her, talk to her.
It'll all be okay
The thing is... but listen... You're not
...but I... what I'm saying...
I'm at Akash's
She hung up
What did you expect?
She'll say Sorry darling!
Enough is enough, Sameer.
Listen to me
Just go there and tell her
these tantrums won't work
If she wants to be with you,
she must follow your wishes
She's challenged your
self-respect, buddy
What are you doing? Be a man!
That's exactly what I'm going to do.
- That's the way to go!
He's dead!
Oh, Priya?
- Please give Sameer the phone
But Sameer hasn't come here. I too am
looking for him since last night
What? Didn't he come there?
Careful man!
Only this eye is working
We need to talk
There's no need for that. I know
what you have to say
You know? - Yes
I spoke to Akash after our talk
Right! And?
He said you weren't at his house
Stop pretending! I can't believe
I did this to myself
I never knew you were such a liar
I don't want to see your
face ever again!
Could I be of any assistance?
It's not a problem at all
Oh God! What's in here?
- My things
Hang on. I'll get it from this side
If just one suitcase has reduced
us to this condition, then...
There's only two more like this
Is that all? Just two more?
Let's go
It's a nice house
It belongs to the company I work for
I am an interior designer...
Tara Jaiswal
What do you do?
I work as a porter on Sundays
And the rest of the week?
Normally if anyone asks me that, I say
anything that pops into my head
But I'll tell you the truth because
I think it might be of interest to you
I don't quite understand?
I mean you have three paintings in your
luggage and that's my vocation
May I see your paintings?
Of course
Where do you live?
The last house down this road.
You can come whenever you wish
Sid, I'm going to the office.
- Just a minute, Ma
I'm coming along. Just drop me off
at Sameer's
By the way, it's Anju's wedding
anniversary today
She'll be very disappointed
if you don't come
Is Siddharth home? - Yes
You are...? - I am Tara
Ma, this is Tara
Well, I'd better be going
Ya, you go ahead, I'll go myself.
All right. But you are coming
this evening, aren't you?
Where? - To Anju's!
Mom, I get extremely bored there
There are very few places in this world
where you don't get bored
Fine! Have it your way.
Please have a seat
I'd like to see your paintings first
The same theme here too
What theme?
I have learnt something about
you today
Something I couldn't see
at our first meeting
What's that?
The thing is, you meet people,
talk to them, laugh...
But there's a world within you...
...full of dreams, of fantasies...
...that you don't share with anyone
I wonder if those, who claim
to know you...
...really know you at all
What makes you say that?
The door is not open...
Entry is forbidden...
The box is tightly bound...
No one can steal anything...
And who can tell what feelings reflect
behind those shut eyelids...
I wonder what other secrets your
paintings hide within them...
Or within you perhaps
Why are you looking at me
like that?
Anyway, which do you think
is your best?
I have yet to create that one
Look at your face!
White as a sheet!
Look, I am very angry right now
and all because of you
Hey! I saved your life and
you are angry with me?
Saved my life?
- Absolutely!
This was bound to happen
Priya would've left you tomorrow
if not today. Know why?
Because she didn't love you,
she loved some other Sameer
He looked like you but was
someone else
You are not that- Sameer. You are the
Sameer I know, Sid knows...
And Priya could only hope to know
If you became that Sameer, our this
Sameer would be defeated!
I never thought of it like that...
- I know
Then pack your bags and let's go
Sid and I are waiting for you
in the car
Where are we going? - Goa!
Goa...?!
The heart wants...
May these sparkling days never end
May we never have to be
without our friends
May our days be full of poetry...
...our evenings dance and
nights sing.
May our time together always
be fun and exciting
May every path we tread
bring us happiness
The heart wants...
May these sparkling days
never end
The heart wants...
May we never have to be
without our friends
Our paths dazzle with their glitter
May this joy and light
be ours by right
Where's Akash?
There... behind the plant
Are you guys staying here too?
Not are... we were.
We are checking out
We've been staying here for a week.
Isn't that right, guys?
Yes, we've been here for a week
But Akash just got here today.
- Yes. I got here today
Akash! It's nice to see you haven't
lost your sense of humour!
Hey Sid, look over there!
Sid, did you hear that?
Someone's calling out my name
Go faster, buddy. Faster
This is the top speed
What an amazing place!
We should come to Goa every year,
for a week at least
What say, Sid?
What are you thinking?
I'm looking at that ship...
...that's about to disappear over
the horizon
The three of us are like that ship
Soon, we'll set out looking
for our destinations...
...and it might just be that
our destinations are different
I don't understand why
you're saying all this
Sid, we are all friends...
...for life
Of course we are
But who knows where life will
take each one of us
Ever wondered, let alone come
here every year for a week...
It may be difficult to meet
even once in 10 years
That won't happen, Sid
We were, are and will be friends.
Always
Anyway, shall we go?
Deepa must be waiting for you
Don't say must be waiting.
She is!
I told her Akash will meet her
by the poolside at 8 sharp!
How strange is this journey!
If you just think...
Each one of us is so unaware...
...of where he is destined to go...
...of what the future
holds for each of us
The heart wants...
May these sparkling days never end
May we never have to be
without our friends
May our days be full of poetry...
...our evenings dance
and nights sing
May our time together always
be fun and exciting
May every path we tread
bring us happiness
Our paths dazzle with their glitter
May this joy and light
be ours by right
Deepa, why do you like Akash
so much?
What do you mean?
Sometimes I wonder why we
like and want someone
Why do you like him?
I don't know... I just do
Even knowing that Akash...
...doesn't love me
Yes... then too
Deepa you are a good-Iooking,
intelligent girl.
You can get anyone you want...
In that case, why can't
I have Akash!
I don't know that...
But I do know that if
you're ever in trouble,
And need Akash's help or support,
he'll do whatever he can for you.
But Deepa, you shouldn't
hope for things that...
Take a look at this sand
The tighter you try to grip it...
...the faster it slips
through your fingers
Have you donated your bag
to the hotel?
Actually, I've decided to
stay back for a few days
What?
Er... Kristine wants me to stay
for some more time
Kristine? that girl who...
Sid! Are you listening? Our friend has
decided to become a hippie!
If you hadn't brought me here,
I'd have never met her
She's Swiss. I was wondering...
why not go there...
...and start a bee farm.
Swiss honey is world famous...
Let's go Akash
What have I done! He was
better off with Priya
One more thing...
Please don't call my house
till I get back
So, did you have fun in Goa?
It was great. Have you been there?
Yes. Many years ago
Whose photographs are these?
Esha... my daughter
Oh, I haven't met her.
Where is she?
She lives with her father
9th April 95... exactly
on my birthday...
My husband gave me a gift...
You do meet your daughter,
don't you?
No
The Court doesn't permit me
to meet my daughter
Why?
My ex-husband is a very rich man
His lawyers were very smart and
capable
With the help of many false
witnesses, he proved...
...that I am not a good mother.
That I'm an alcoholic
An irresponsible woman
who drinks
You're nothing like that!
Oh for you to have been
the judge!
Anyway, what else
did you do there?
I'd like to paint you
Paint me?
Be back in two minutes
Are you going somewhere?
Sorry, I have to go
I just got a call from the site.
There's a problem
Have you given any thought
to your future?
No
I know it's my fault...
...I always thought, I'd give
you some time... You needed it.
It's my pampering that
has spoilt you
If this goes on...
You'll definitely have signed
a cheque till my retirement
Dad, there are more things
to life than signing cheques
Really! And what are these things?
I don't know yet but the moment
I do, you'll be the first to know
I have had enough of your jokes
I've decided that you will go
to Australia
Cool! Another holiday?
You'll manage our business
there
Mom, Dad's joking now
No, Akash. Dad is serious
and you better be serious too
You are going to Sydney
And you will manage the office there
Sameerji's Mummyji is on the phone
Akash Baba says that...
Yes, Aunty
What's wrong with Sameer?
Nothing's wrong with Sameer.
He's perfectly OK
What OK!? He's shut himself
in his room
He hasn't eaten and just
doesn't come out
Sameer is in Bombay?
Didn't you all come back
last night
Yes, Aunty. It was last night
but... I'm so distracted now...
Akash, are you and Sameer on drugs?
Of course not, Aunty. Don't worry.
I'll be there right away
The least you could've done was call.
I didn't know what to say to your Mom
What's happened to you?
I'm in no mood to talk now
Okay. How's Kristine?
Don't even mention her name
in front of me!
Why? What happened?
Get it off your chest
It's not good for health
to suppress such emotions
Well, after the two of left
the other day...
I met Kristine on the beach
It felt so good...
Just Kristine and me...
I loved her so much...
How happy I was...
We watched the sunset and she
came back to the hotel with me
I invited her in
I could never have imagined
what happened next
I don't think she was from
Switzerland either
I'm glad to have amused you guys!
That truck driver who gave me a ride
to Bombay was far more sympathetic!
You came back in a truck!?
What did you think?
That I sit on this pillow every day?
I'm pissed off travelling 12 hours
in a truck
Mother, he is Mr. Shankaran.
Art India magazines.
I was telling Siddharth about
my friend who lives in Kasauli
He hosts a painting workshop
every year
And you feel that he must
go there
Absolutely
It'll be a very good experience
for him
Oh, you're here!
You're a strange boy!
you invite me and act surprised when I come.
Ma, this is Tara!
Tara Jaiswal. You introduced us before
How long will you go around
with that glum face...
Come. Let me introduce you
to these sweet girls
Forget it man.
I'm not in the mood
Are you fine?
Look... Kristine!
Do you like it?
I like them all
It's difficult to say
which one is your best
I haven't painted my best yet
Why not?
You don't seem to have the time?
On such a big day in your life
I've to agree to your wish.
Tell me, when you will
start my painting?
Tomorrow
Wait, I'll be out in a minute.
- No problem
What season is this in which the
heart blooms like a flower.
...in which the colours merge...
...and all the fragrances
blend
Moonlight, brooks
and clouds...
Songs, rain
and butterflies...
They all seem favourable to me
What season is this in which
the heart blooms like a flower
Oh look!
Banks of a river...
A bird calls out
to another bird
Look, at the river itself...
She flows on to unite
with the sea
All these journeys
are part of love's caravan
What season is this in which
the heart blooms like a flower
Oh how
can I explain...
How can I make you understand
what love is!
There are no attachments
in love
And neither
are there any barriers
Love's saga is extraordinary
What season is this in which
the heart blooms like a flower
...in which all the colours merge...
...and all the fragrances
blend
Moonlight, brooks
and clouds...
Songs, rain
and butterflies...
They all seem favourable to me
What season is this in which
the heart blooms like a flower
Greetings, Aunty.
Are you going out, Sameer?
Ya, to Akash's... Why?
I'll be back
Mom! What's the matter?
The fact is, Nareshji's daughter
Pooja is coming here
And we want the two of you to...
What! Fixing my marriage...!
An arranged marriage!
No, Mom. Not for me
Why not? Your Daddy and I had
an arranged marriage
Listen to me. We are not forcing
you to get married
We have known them for years
And we thought we'd turn friendship
into a marriage alliance
You don't lose anything by
meeting Pooja, do you?
Okay. But you know my answer.
And that's NO!
Who is it, Sameer?
Er... Sameer, we have something
important to discuss
Nareshji, is that all right?
Anyway, they'll get bored
sitting with us oldies
Are they your friends?
Please sit down
This is Akash and this is Sid
Seems like a deep friendship
Either the friendship is deep
or it's a 3-D photograph
Pooja, you do know why
you're here, don't you?
Yes. Mom and Dad told me
Look, honestly speaking...
When Mom told me about this...
I felt it wasn't right at first...
...but now... I'm so happy you said no to
this arranged marriage bullshit!
I think marriages shouldn't be
made like this
It's so important to love somebody
to get married
What do you think?
Yes, absolutely
Why? Are you in love with
someone?
There is this guy in my life
But I guess I don't love him
enough so far to marry him
I pretty much feel the same...
...but not about the guy in your life!
And then?
Then what!
She went home
It's a problem man
Please don't tell me you've
fallen for her after all this!
Look, Sameer...
I have no doubt whatsoever
you have fallen in love with her
But I'm equally sure that after
3 months...
...you'll be in love with some other
girl
No, Akash
I always thought I knew
what love was
I realized today that I was
completely wrong
Is that so!
Akash, when Pooja told me about
that guy in her life...
For the first time I thought about
all those girls in my life...
I was attracted to all of them...
But I was wrong to think
the attraction was love
And now you love Pooja?
Yes. That's it!
I love Pooja
Then tell her
Take my advice. Don't say
anything to anyone
There's no trusting you
Today it's Pooja,
tomorrow it'll be some Ahuja!
How did you know it's
my birthday?
Didn't you mention it?
I am so happy today
Guess what? Esha called me
She is coming to see me today
My daughter is coming here...
Sid, she remembered it's
my birthday today
I'll be seeing her after 5 years!
I've cooked everything myself.
I baked a cake
I'm so happy
Is Esha coming alone or your...
Oh no. She told him she's going to
a friend's birthday party...
Because Ajay will never let her
come here
Would you like to meet her?
It'll make me happy
How dare you teach my daughter
to lie? Have you no shame?
Thank God I heard Esha
talk to you over the phone
Why don't you stay away from her?
I am her mother!
You were her mother but now
Kiran is her mother
It'd be wise of you to understand
this
Don't ever try to meet Esha again
Not unless you want me to take
you to court... again
You understand what I'm getting at,
don't you?
He tells me I am not Esha's mother!
That Esha is not my daughter!
I am her mother...
He married again
He destroyed all my dreams.
I said nothing
Because I had everything...
I had my Esha
I have nothing at all
I am nothing. Nothing.
You know, crying doesn't suit
you at all
What else can I do!
You can come with me
You two must be wondering where
Siddharth has brought you!
No such thing. We'd go
anywhere to eat cake
Will you dance with me?
Where?
- Right here there's lot of space, come.
Sid, we've reached your house
What?
You're joking, right?
Hey Akash, he's serious man!
Have you gone mad?
Sid, my knowledge of such
things is a bit sad but...
...this is a but much, isn't it?
Is that because she's older?
No. I mean that too
Wait a minute! Why are we even
discussing this nonsense?
Because I thought that may be
you guys would understand
Hey Sid! Understand what?
You say you love a woman who
is 10 to 15 years older than you...
...has a daughter, had a husband
You've told us she has a
drinking problem
What should we understand?
- Just this...
I know all this and still
love her
But Sid, think about it.
This isn't love, it's insanity
No. This is love
I don't expect her to be mine
or marry me
I don't expect any such thing
Even if she doesn't love me,
it's okay because I...
okay! I get it
Remember, Sameer? Even I had
started off like this
Started what off?
Oh. Of course.
Okay, Sid. If that's what it's about
then I have no objection
In fact she's perfect for you
She's experienced, lives alone.
You visit her everyday
Learn from him, Sameer
Really, Sid. You couldn't have
chosen better...
How disgusting can you get!
Here I am telling you I love her and
you make it sound so sick and dirty
We don't have to approve
everything our friends do
But there is a line in every
friendship that shouldn't be crossed
And you have crossed it today
At some point in life everyone
experiences true love
Then all the things you said...
about her age and stuff...
They don't mean anything.
They all seem trivial
You won't understand this today
But some day you will know...
You don't decide to fall in love
It just happens
Are you finished?
Sameer, are you coming?
I still remember that night
I never thought things would go
that far
I couldn't sleep all night
I went and met Akash
the next morning
These things happen
between friends
Let's go meet Sid.
He must be feeling bad too
You're sure to run into him
somewhere
What'll you do? Ignore him?
You're coming to meet Sid
Leave me alone, Sameer!
I have to see Sid
He's gone
Where? - Kasauli
They called yesterday to say his
application was accepted. So he...
What is it, Sameer?
Is everything alright?
Of course. I should go
I didn't realise that things
would never be the same again
You went to Kasauli... A week later,
Akash left for Australia
Take care of yourself
You remember the name of the man
who'll receive you in Sydney?
Mr. Mehta... Relax, Dad.
I remember
Bye. I'll call you from there
I must tell you something
- What's it?
I always made fun of your
endless romantic entanglements
Never stopped to think how you
must feel
You know I was just kidding,
don't you?
Don't worry about it
You weren't the only one who was
kidding
You remember Shalini?
I remember Shalini...
And Rohit's punch as well
I knew she was Rohit's fiancee
Why didn't you tell me?
Why didn't you stop me?
I said Hi
Where are you going?
This flight goes to Sydney
But where are you going?
How strange! All three of us
are going to Sydney
Three?
Sure. You, me, and this flight
You do know you're insane,
don't you?
I'm really sorry about
the other night
I was just kidding
So what are you...
What are you doing in Sydney?
Dad has a business there he
wants me to manage...
Let's see how long it lasts now.
And you?
My uncle lives there
My mother's brother.
I'm visiting him
He's nothing like Rohit, is he!
What does he do?
Have you been to Sydney before?
Do you always ask so many
questions?
Yes. Have you been to Sydney
before?
Yes
Good. You can show me around
Wait a minute. Don't you know
anybody else there?
Of course. There is a Mr. Mehta
And won't it be fun hanging out
with him?
I said I'm sorry
Okay but I will have to ask
my uncle
But he won't refuse.
Why?
Because I have bought him a gift!
I'm fine but please stop
calling me uncle now
You've grown up which makes us
practically the same age
So, is it a business trip?
We have an export business and
Dad's exported me here to handle it
Exports? Sounds very boring, man
That's what I think too
Personally, I prefer something more
adventurous...
...like wild life photography
You like photography?
Mum says the first word I said
wasn't Papa or Mama...
It was camera!
I'm Steve
Steve? - Satyadev Mehta
I've organized a car for you.
I'll get your trolley
Okay Shalini, I'll take your leave.
Bye, Mahesh
Here's my card. If you need
anything in Sydney, call me
Well, I'd better leave now.
I'm sure you want to rest
I'll send the driver to pick you
up tomorrow
Yes, I'll tell Mr. Mehta
Dad wants you to send him
a copy of the new contract
You are coming to the meeting
tomorrow, aren't you?
Can you give me our transaction
file?
I'd like to know a little more about
them before the meeting
I'll send you the file right away
Is there a good restaurant around
here?
Being alone in a new city
can be so boring
But you aren't alone!
Who said I was bored?
Who'd have thought that
someday you
and me would be sitting
here like friends
Especially after all that happened...
So how is Rohit?
He's fine. I spoke to him
this morning
I told him I met you on the flight
and...
And he doesn't like you meeting
me! Right?
But you're here.
Why?
Akash, you don't know Rohit.
He doesn't like me meeting
any boys
But Rohit is a good guy
He has a few faults but then,
don't we all. Me... you...
Faults... and me!
So tell me about yourself
What do you want to know?
Of course I have. But not for
more than 2 weeks
Then there's another girlfriend...
another 2 weeks...
And then another...
stop! I understand how your
girlfriend system works
What I don't understand is...
why?
The fact is, I've seen many of my
friends with their "beloveds"
They have everything but love
for each other
That's why I think I am better off
as I am
No questions... no answers
I don't ask Rohit questions,
nor do I demand answers
But he asks questions.
He demands answers
I never said it's always
the girl's fault
But relationships just get like that.
Start with joy and end in grief
I see! So this is the result of
an end in grief
Now I've understood your
2 weeks formula!
No! It's nothing of the sort
I have consciously decided not to
fall in love and ruin my life
But love isn't about decisions.
It just happens
Then I don't let it happen to me
Give it some time. I'm sure
it will some day
Why? Are you proposing?
How was your day?
Akash is nuts
Turn it down guys.
It's my wife-to-be
How are you?
Hopefully a little less drunk
Did you get my message?
Where were you?
I met Akash for lunch
I told you not to meet him!
Why don't you listen to me?
Are you yelling at me in front
of your friends?
I am coming there. It'll take some
time but I will be there
As you wish, Rohit. Bye
Pooja, I was in the neighbourhood
and I thought...
Pooja, if you aren't doing
anything else...
Pooja, I was in the neighbour...
Bye mom, I'll call later
Fine. And you?
Subodh, this is Sameer.
Sameer, this is Subodh
Are you waiting for someone?
Yes. But it seems like
they won't show up now
So tell me... what's the plan
after dinner?
No plan
Come on, let's do something
What say, Subodh?
I'm sorry. I've made it a habit
to sleep by 10
One night won't change
your habit
Come on, pal. Anyway,
it's Sunday tomorrow
I know. Thing is I've to wake up at
5 and do Yoga
Then some jogging and breakfast
at 8 sharp
And since it's Sunday...
...we spend the day at Kumar uncle's
beach house
I'll be right back
It's time for his bathroom break,
right?
He isn't that bad
So where are you off to?
Let's see...
If Time Table doesn't want to
come, may be you can join me
I'm sure I can...
If I call you sometime...
Wow! What're we celebrating?
You don't remember?
It was on this day five months ago
that I told you what I felt for you
To Subodh and Pooja!
What's the situation like?
- Pretty intense
Really, Mahesh
There were such intense scenes
in the film! So moving...
Please cut out the performance
And forgive me for taking you
to see such a good film!
You see! That's my biggest problem
I can't bear watching good films
Yes. You only like those
wham bang action films
Anyway, that's all you can
understand...
...because they don't require you
to use your brains or heart!
You need plenty of brains for
these love stories
She sits here shedding tears,
he sits there sighing...
...what's all this lovey- dovey
stuff about anyway!
You won't understand
What're you doing man, let's go
Wonder why
people fall in love
Wonder why people
are ready to die for someone
Wonder why
people fall in love
Wonder why people
are ready to die for someone
Wonder why,
Oh wonder why...
Wonder why... why... why!
Just think about it,
there is only grief in love
As for love's cruelty,
it's past counting
When in love
your head must remain bowed
Even when in pain
you have to smile
Why fill your own life
with poison?
Wonder why
people fall in love
Wonder why,
Oh wonder why
Wonder why why... why...
Without love
what's left in life
A person is Ionely
Without love
what's there in life
A person is Ionely
Love brings colour
into your life
Love brings beauty
People fall in love
but hide it
Wonder why they fear
expressing it openly
Wonder why,
Oh wonder why...
Wonder why why why!
Love is just
needless trouble
Love is beautiful
in every aspect
We are all better off
far away from love
Love's every form
is the assured truth
He that tests love's
waters...
...neither drowns nor floats
Wonder why?
Everyone but everyone
falls in love
Wonder why only you
keep avoiding it
Wonder why...
Wonder why why why!
Tell me something Shalini
Why're you so scared of
sitting on these rides?
I m not scared
I think only those who aren't right
in their heads enjoy these rides
Interesting excuse
You need courage to sit on
these rides! You need guts
But don't worry. There are many
cowards like you around here
Look. There's one right there
It's not like that at all
If it isn't like that, then get on
that ride with me
Why? No guts?
It's getting late
I'm going on that ride
If you want, you can come with me.
Or sit here and get bored
Absolutely no guts
Hurry. We can catch this train
Really Shalini! How could you
scare that poor old man!
How did it go?
Really well. They like my work
And... they want me to
come back
That's great
When will you have to go?
I've just returned and you're
asking about my leaving
Did you talk to Sameer?
No. Why?
He came over the morning
you left
He seemed very troubled
What did he say?
- Nothing
When did you get back?
How are you? How's everything?
Great. How are things with you
man?
It's a very long story
Let's go up and talk
Okay, so here's the situation
You are pretty good friends.
Hang out together
But you still haven't told her
how you feel
I've tried very hard...
But the words just don't come out
Didn't she have a boyfriend?
Yup. She did... but not anymore
I don't know what Pooja saw
in him
I mean he was sweet
but what a bore!
One day I made the mistake of
going for a drive with them
See this place...
I met Pooja for the first time
on 15th September right here
Exactly 7 days later, we came here
to have ice cream... 22nd September
You wouldn't remember the time,
would you?
Of course I remember.
It was exactly 5.55
That's not all
He'd buy her a balloon
everyday
Balloon...?
Yes. You know those heart shaped
ones you get at signals
It's okay but...
Everyday!
One balloon a day!
I knew the guy was deranged
If you love Pooja so much,
why haven't you told her?
I was afraid...
What if Pooja says no?
I'd even lose this friendship
we share now...
and be all alone
You weren't here.
Nor was Akash
Anyway, you're here now
And I feel stronger knowing
that you're here for me
I'm always here for you, Sameer
Then... shall I tell her today?
Tell her
Pooja, there's something
I need to tell you
I wonder what if the arranging
incident hadn't happened
If we hadn't met the way we
did...
If I had met you somewhere else,
would we be the same as we are now?
And if we weren't the way we are,
how else would we be?
If you thought differently
about me...
...if I thought differently about
you, what'd happen?
What's happening now?
...What am I saying?
Just a lot of ifs!
What's the matter?
The matter is just that...
I'm falling in love with you
I agree that we don't know
each other very well
If you trust me at all, believe
that I am telling the truth
I look everywhere for her.
But I still haven't found her
Where is the girl
in whose love I can believe?
She who loves only me
She must be even ready
to say...
"O listen, you are the one
who has my heart"
Oh, where is that girl?
She who lives in your dream
as love's beautiful embodiment...
You will find her someday
or other
Just look here and there
Let's both go and find her...
This angel, this fairy,
this damsel so dainty...
...who upon seeing,
you will say
She is right here!
I wonder why
I had this thought...
Could you be the
dream girl?
You have all the graces
that I search for everywhere
I think you are deluded
I wonder what you think I am
I am no angel or fairy
nor any celestial nymph
Don't have any such
illusions
I look everywhere for her.
But I still haven't found her
Where is the girl
in whose love I can believe?
Suppose I say to you...
All I think of
is you and only you
You must know
this is what I desire...
...you must be with me,
only with me
Oh, what have you made me believe!
Oh, how you make my heart beat!
You melt my body and soul...
...reciting this saga of yours
I look everywhere for her.
But I still haven't found her
Where is the girl
in whose love I can believe?
Oh, where is that girl?
That girl is here!
Where is that girl?
- That girl is here!
I can't believe that it's already
time for you to leave
Don't worry, Mom.
I'll be back soon
Three months is not soon
And that's this time
You don't know how long
you'll be gone next time
Siddharth... have you thought about
marriage?
Mom!
What Mom!
Some other time, okay?
- But why? Why not now?
It's just... forget it, Mom.
You won't understand
I'm your mother! If I can't
understand you, who else will?
Is there someone you like?
Sid, what's the matter?
You've never hidden anything
from me
Yes, Ma. But there are some things
that you just can't tell somebody
Yes there are...
But I can see there's something
eating away at you inside
Will you keep it bottled up inside
all your life?
Ma, I'm telling you
you won't understand!
Why won't I understand?
Try telling me
What is this thing that I don't
have the right to know?
What's the matter?
That Tara Jaiswal?
I've met her so many times...
But... she...
When did this start?
I don't know when...
I won't let you ruin your life!
Have you any inkling of what
you are saying?
My son has fallen in love with
a woman who...
You were right I wouldn't
understand
And what has she told you,
that she loves you?
She must've seduced you with her
sad stories
What did she say to you?
- She said nothing!
She doesn't even know that I...
Your mother is absolutely right,
Siddharth
Don't ruin your life over me. And the
little peace I have left in my life...
Please don't take it away
from me
Go away! - Please listen to me
I don't want to hear anything
Have I ever made you feel
that I love you...
...or want a relationship
with you?
No
Then what made you think...
...that you and I could...
...have any such relationship?
This is the problem with your
generation
You all think anything goes.
But that's not so, Siddharth
Why just me?
You have also caused your mother
a lot of pain
Please sit down
I'm so sorry that I caused you
and my mother such pain
I'm sorry you had to hear
all this because of me
But it's true that I love you
It's also true that I never
wanted you to know it
Because I knew that you...
...would never be able to understand
I just want to see you happy
And if knowing the truth
has caused you pain today...
All I can say is, that wasn't
my intention
Sid, please leave now
After the workshop...
I think I'll go stay at uncle's
farm house for a while
It's a good place to paint
Will you come with me?
I don't want to go without you
Just a minute...
You look very lovely
So, why are we here?
To prove to you that a thing called
love does exist in this world
Don't you ever give up?
Shut up and lets go in
Why are we here?
- To watch an opera
Yes, but why?
You'll know when the time comes
The girl's name is Cressida
and the boy is Troilus
They love each other very much
But Troilus must go now
He has to go to war for his country
Cressida is afraid something may
happen to him
Troilus is telling her
nothing will happen to him
This is the spirit of Troilus...
standing at heaven's gate
But he doesn't want to go inside
He is asking God for one day
He wants to meet Cressida for
one last time
And tell her how much he loves her
If he is given one day...
He is willing to die a thousand
deaths
Shut your eyes, Akash
Think...
Who is it...
...to spend that one day with, you
are willing to die a thousand deaths
Who is it, Akash?
No so easily!
You still haven't told me
who you saw
You seem quite sure that I
saw someone?
Yes. Because today for
the first time...
...you're talking less
and thinking more!
Then listen
I saw her...
And I felt...
...perhaps this is what
they call love
I wanted to touch her...
...hold her in my arms...
I saw such innocence
in her eyes...
...like I see in your eyes now
Her voice...
...had the kind of magic
your voice has
I can still feel the fragrance
of her breath...
...like I can feel
in your breath now
Who was she?
That fat opera singer!
Shalini, come inside... at once!
I think the two of you should
talk alone
Where had you gone?
- To the opera
With Akash!
How many times have I told you
not to meet him!
Rohit, will you keep telling me
all my life...
...who I should or should not meet!
Yes. I will
And you will never see Akash
again. You got that?
Rohit, I need some time to think
and you need it too
Shalini had called.
She said it's important
Hi, Rohit. It's Akash
Is Shalini there? She had called
I know. We are going back...
to get married
Can I speak to Shalini?
That's good news
Akash, we are going back tomorrow
Can you come for dinner tonight?
I don't know. Bye
Hey, Akash! We thought you
weren't going to make it
They're beautiful. Thanks
What will you drink?
We can drink later. Let's eat first.
I'm starving
Shalini, have you told
Mahesh Uncle...
...how you and Akash met?
No?
Really, Mahesh Uncle...
I don't know what you'd have
done if you were there
What happened?
It was at my graduation
party
Shalini was with me
Perhaps Akash didn't know
that...
Sorry for the punch
No, Rohit. It was my fault
But to tell you the truth,
I think I was lucky
What do you mean?
I mean, if Shalini was with me...
...and someone had acted fresh...
I'd have killed him
That is...
If Shalini was with you
Hey, wait...
You're coming to our wedding,
aren't you?
No, I can't make it. There's a lot
of work to be done
Some friend you are!
Anyway, don't forget to call us to
your wedding
We'll definitely be there
I'm not going to get married
Why?
It's necessary to love someone
to get married
And I believe...
...this thing called love doesn't
exist in the world
Shalini and I love each other
That's why we're getting married.
Isn't that so, Shalini?
You both shouldn't ask each other
this question. Ask yourself
I better go
You left your jacket with me
the other night
Some day I want to tell you why
I am marrying Rohit
Why? What's the need to tell me?
I need to...
Because we both know...
...that night at the opera,
when you shut your eyes...
...it wasn't the fat opera singer
you saw
Loneliness
This Ioneliness...
Why have I stumbled on
the path of love
All my dreams lie shattered
A sense of gloom lies heavy
Every joy is be numbed
My very life is lost
I am being punished
for loving you
Loneliness...
Loneliness stretches over
miles and miles
In my dream I saw
a hand in my hand
Now I am blinded by the
shards of a shattered dream
Someone was here yesterday
but today there is no one
Like a cobra's venomous hiss
it envelopes my very breath...
...this Ioneliness
has brought tears to my eyes
Oh how could my hope for
something be so futile
I've embarked on a journey
to which there is no destination
Where should I go?
To whom shall I explain?
What I had wanted...
And why I ended up with...
...this Ioneliness
Loneliness
deeply dark as the night
Why have I stumbled on
the path of love
All my dreams lie shattered
A sense of gloom lies heavy
Every joy is be numbed
My very life is lost
I am being punished
for loving you
Loneliness...
Loneliness stretches over
miles and miles
Hello, Aunty. Is Sameer home?
Who is this?
You want to talk to Sameer
and you've called Siddharth!
How are you?
I... I'm okay, Aunty
He's gone to Kasauli. Give me
your number. I'll give it to him
No, it's okay.
I'll call him
How are you, son?
I'm okay, Dad
What's wrong? Are you unwell?
No, it's nothing like that
Been working all day...
I'm tired, that's all
Come back home, Akash
What's wrong, Akash?
I've never seen you like this
before
I'm in love, Dad
So what's the problem?
She is marrying somebody else
Have you told her you love her?
No
Does she love you?
Yes, she does
Has she told you?
Akash, you must tell her
how you feel
No
Why not?
She is marrying somebody else
There are many things in this world
that are beyond our understanding
When a person decides something...
...there must be a reason for that
decision
You say that the girl loves you
but is marrying someone else
Have you tried to find out
why she's doing it?
What's the reason for her decision?
How's Shalini?
She isn't happy
And how could she be?
She is marrying Rohit
but loves you
Did she tell you that?
- No
Did you ever tell me you love her?
Then why's she getting married?
Rohit's father and Shalini's father
were business partners
Shalini was six when her parents
were killed in a car accident
I was her only relative but
I wasn't able to support her
Rohit's parents took her in...
...not only into their home
but their hearts and their life
They've done a lot for her
If they want her to marry Rohit,
Shalini can't refuse
What else can she do?
On one hand are the people who've
given her the life she's living
On the other hand is a man...
She doesn't even know if he loves
her or not
Akash, what are you doing man!
Go and tell her you love her
Akash, only you know what
you have to do
Just know this. Tonight is
the Sangeet function...
...and tomorrow the wedding
Whatever your decision,
you must make it today
Will you marry me?
Not even if I tell you that
I love you?
Shalini...
I love you and only you
My every breath...
...every heartbeat...
...every moment,
is for you, Shalini
I'm sure that I was born
so that I could love you
And you were born to become mine
You are mine, Shalini
And if you ask your heart...
...you will know that I speak
the truth
What's going on! Who is this boy?
I'll tell you
He is Akash Malhotra,
A.K. Malhotra's son...
...who's been after Shalini,
wagging his tail
I hit him once but I guess
it wasn't enough, huh?
I won't leave you today!
You will do no such thing, Rohit.
I want to speak to Shalini first
No, Rohit! You wait here.
- But Dad! This is my life...
Mahesh, I feel very hurt today
I always thought that Shalini was
my daughter
But today I feel that she has
never thought of us as her own
She wants to repay her debt to us
by marrying Rohit
All right
Shalini, you must repay us
For looking after you from
childhood till now... you owe us
For giving you whatever you
asked for... you owe us
For shielding you from
even a hint of trouble...
...you owe us
Now if you want to repay all that
you owe us... see us happy...
Then marry Akash
Can you do this much for me?
Come...
Take care of her.
She is my daughter
Just a minute, Dad
You can't do this! Mom, why
aren't you saying anything?
Let her go, Rohit
You care about Shalini's happiness
but don't give a damn about mine!
Rohit, if Shalini is not happy
being with you...
...how can you ever be happy?
This can't happen to me!
I won't allow this!
What are you doing?
I love Akash
All his life he said...
I won't say "I love you" to anyone
And when he had to say it...
It was at someone's wedding
in front of 300 people!
Did you call him?
What did he say?
He wasn't home
I told you he won't come
Can I talk to Sid?
How are you?
Fine. How are you?
Forgive me
I must apologise too
Some other time.
It's my turn today
You haven't changed
at all
Ya. Anyway, it's hard to improve
on perfection
Where are you? When can we meet?
Today. Now. This very moment
Now... there's no pain...
nor any fear
I feel good
It's peaceful here
You're a good boy, Siddharth
You always stood by me
You want me to be happy,
don't you...
Then... you be happy
You will, won't you?
I will
Life is so strange
Some relationships...
...don't have any name
You and I will always...
Hey Sid, look at your ship
It was so small 2 years ago.
Look how much it's grown
If you guys wanted to be by
yourselves, you should've told us
See! I'm getting told off because
of you
I've been telling you, let's go
What?
Come on
Come on man